{
    "questions":[

        {
            "id":"1",
            "question": "When you subtract 1,995 from 4,008, the answer is equal to", 
            "answer": "2013"

        }, 
        {
            "id":"2",
            "question": "How many milliliters in one liter?",
            "answer": "1000 millilitres"
        },
        {
            "id": "3",
            "question": "Round 312.92 to the nearest whole number.",
            "answer":"313"
        },
        {
            "id": "4",
            "question": "If you add 1,000 to 29,898, you obtain",
            "answer": "30,898"
        },

        {
            "id": "5",
            "question": "Convert 5/10 to decimal.",
            "answer": "0.5"
        },
        {
            "id":"6",
            "question" : "There are 61 boxes of pencils in a store. There are 14 pencils in each box. How many pencils are in the store?",
            "answer":  "854 pencils"
        },

        {
            "id" : "7",
            "question": "There are 24 hours in one day, and 3,600 seconds in one hour. How many seconds are in one day?",
            "answer": "86,400 seconds"
        },

        {
            "id": "8",
            "question":"Julia read a book in 20 days. She read 16 pages every day for the first 15 days, and 18 pages everyday for the last 5 days. How many pages did Julia read?",
            "answer": "330 pages"
        },

        {
            "id": "9",
            "question":"64 sweets are put in boxes that contain 8 sweets each. How many boxes are needed?",
            "answer": "8 boxes"
        },

        {
            "id": "10",
            "question":"If 6 children share 145 sweets equally, how many sweets will remain?",
            "answer": "1"
        },

        {
            "id": "11",
            "question":"What is n if 9 x n = 108",
            "answer": "12"
        },

        {
            "id": "12",
            "question":"What is the value of (14 + 5) - (5 - 2)",
            "answer": "16"
        },

        {
            "id": "13",
            "question":"2 x (14 + 5) - 7 =",
            "answer": "31"
        },

        {
            "id": "14",
            "question":"What is the value of 23 - (10 - a) if a = 5?",
            "answer": "18"
        },
        
        {
            "id" : "15",
            "question": "If z + y = 20 and y = 5, what is z?",
            "answer" :"15"
        },

        {
            "id" : "16",
            "question": "What is S if 6 x 4 = 3 x S?",
            "answer" :"8"
        },

        {
            "id" : "17",
            "question": "A large box contains 18 small boxes and each small box contains 25 chocolate bars. How many chocolate bars are in the large box?",
            "answer" :"450 chocolate bars"
        },

        {
            "id" : "18",
            "question": "It takes John 25 minutes to walk to the car park and 45 to drive to work. At what time should he get out of the house in order to get to work at 9:00 a.m.?",
            "answer" :"7:50 a.m."
        },


        {
            "id":"19",
            "question":"John spent 3/5 of his money on books and 1/3 of the remainder on a wallet. If John had $16 left, how much did he have at first?",
            "answer":"$60"
        },
        {
            "id":"20",
            "question":"There are 836 students in a school. 7/10 of the boys and 7/8 of the girls take bus to school. The number of boys who do not take bus is twice the number of girls who do not take bus. How many girls do not take bus?",
            "answer":"57 girls"
        }
        
    ]
 }  